A Finding Aid to the Federal Art Project, Photographic Division Collection, circa 1920-1965, bulk 1935-1942, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 9.6 Linear feet Boxes 1-24
  - Cerny, George, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Cervantez, Pedro, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    includes photo of Cervantez
  - Champanier, Abram August, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Chan, H., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Chanase, Dane, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
    includes photos of Chanase, circa 1942
  - Chaney, Ruth, circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Chapin, Cornelia Van Auken, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Charat, Bernard S., 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Charlot, Jean, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chavez, Edward, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cheney, Philip, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Chernoff, Vadim, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Chin, Chee, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Chodorow, Eugene, circa 1937-circa 1939, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
    includes photos of Chodorow and August Henkel, circa 1939
  - Christopher, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Citron, Minna, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Claflin, Majel G., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Claney, Howard, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Clark, Fletcher, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Cogan, Martin, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Cohen, Toby, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Cole, Robert B., 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Cole, Thomas Casilear, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Colgan, Joseph, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Collins, Pat, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
    photo of Collins, 1939 April
  - Collins, Rosamond, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Connaway, Jay H., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Constant, George, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cook, Howard, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cooke, Regina Tatum, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Copeland, Lila, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Copen, Herman, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Corbino, Jon, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Cormis, Jack, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Corso, Antonio, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Costa, Francis, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    includes photo of Costa, 1939
  - Couse, E., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Covey, Arthur, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Cox, George, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Craig, Martin, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Crimi, Alfred D., circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
    includes possible photo of Crimi
  - Crimi, Charles, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Criss, Francis, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    includes photo of Criss, October 1930
  - Cronbach, Robert M., circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cross, Louise, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Crow, Claude, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Csoka, Stephen, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cunning, John, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - D'Agostino, Vincent, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Dames, Chester, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Daniel, Lewis C., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Daniels, Jacob F., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Darnell, Janet, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Datz, A. Mark, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Davey, Randall, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Davidson, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Davis, C. W., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Charles, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Hubert, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Davis, Lew E., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Davis, Richard, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Davis, Stuart, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
    includes photo of Davis, January 1939
  - Davis, Wyatt, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dawson, Omer G., circa 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Day, Selma, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Dean, Bob, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dearing, Elizabeth, circa 1938-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
    includes photos of Dearing, circa 1939
  - De Brennecke, Nina, circa 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - De Cordoba, Mathilde, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - De Felipe, Juan, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dehn, Adolf and Virginia, circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    includes photos of Adolf and Virginia Dehn, Reginald Marsh and Elizabeth Olds
  - De La Guadagne, Armand, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Delgado, Eduardo, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Delman, Elias Ben, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - De Lorenzo, Fred, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - De Martini, Joseph, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - De Rivera, Jose, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
    includes photos of De Rivera
  - De Rocco, Jovan, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Derup, Karl, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - De Vault, David S., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - De Vegh, G., circa 1935-circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Diener, Irving, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dill, Elaine, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Di Nicola, Joseph, circa 1935-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Dirk, Nathaniel, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    photo of Dirk, 1937 October
  - Di Tore, Salvatore, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dodd, Lamar, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Doi, Isami, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Doktor, Raphael, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Donaldson, Alice Willits, 1938-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Donskoy-Kallman, I., 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Downer, Kenneth, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Drake, Venetia, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dreis, Edward, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Drewes, Werner, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Driggs, Elsie, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Du Bois, Guy Pène, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Duhmart, G., 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Dunham, Francis, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Dunstan, W. H., 1923; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Durant, Helen, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dwight, Mabel, circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Eaton, Dorothy, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Eby, Kerr, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Edie, Stuart Carson, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Egri, Ruth, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
    includes photo of Egri, 1937 April
  - Egri, Theodore, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Ehlreich, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Eichenberg, Fritz, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Eilshemius, Louis, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Elliot, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Emanuel, Herzl, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Emergen, Fred, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Emerson, C., 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Emerson, Sybil, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Emery, Irene, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 51)
    photo of Emery, circa 1937
  - Engers, Leon, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Ennis, George Pearse, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 53)
    includes photos of Ennis, circa 1936
  - Ensel, Henry, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Enters, Angna, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 55)
    photo of Enters
  - Esman, Betty, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Etellback, A., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Etting, Emlen, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Euffa, Ray, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Everett, Roberta, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Evergood, Philip, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 61)
    includes photos of Evergood, 1938 May, 1939 June
  - Faber, Arthur, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Faber, J. W., 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fabry, Alois, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fastovsky, Isaac, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fay, Hans, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Faye, Harold, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Federici, Gaetano, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Feinstein, David, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ferrara, Vincent, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Ferrugio, Remo, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Ferstadt, Louis, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    includes photos of Ferstadt
  - Ficini, Gino, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Fidaroff, Simon, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Fields, Earl Thomas, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Fields, Mitchell, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Filmus, Tully, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Filtzer, Hyman, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Finta, Alexander, circa 1936-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    includes photos of Finta, 1939 June
  - Fiorillo, Anthony, 1938-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Flannery, Vaughn, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Fleishman, Gertrude, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Fleri, Joseph C., circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Flint, Alice, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Flint, Leroy, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Floegel, Alfred E., 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Floherty, John J., circa 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Fogel, Seymour, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
    includes photos of Fogel
  - Folinsbee, John Fulton, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Forbes, Donald, 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Fortess, Karl Eugene, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Fossum, Sydney Glen, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Frank, Bena Virginia, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Frankel, Josephine, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Frankel, Max, 1938-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Franklin, George, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Freeman, Don, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Hy, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Frelinghuysen, Thomas T. K., circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - French, Jared, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Friedman, Arnold, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Friedman, Mark, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Friedman, Sidney, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Frisch, Sari, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Fuller, Robert, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Furedi, Lily, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Furness, Richard, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Gaige, Richard, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Gallagher, Michael J., circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Galos, Ben, circa 1940-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ganso, Emil, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Gantman, Edna, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Garcia, Estella, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Garrison, Robert, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
    includes photo of Garrison, 1939 May
  - Gasparo, Oronzo, 1938, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gassner, Mordi, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Gaulois, Helen, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
    includes photos of Gaulois, 1938
  - Gelb, Donald, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Gelfand, Sydney, 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Gellert, Hugo, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Gelman, Aaron, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Gentle, Robert, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Gerbino, Rosario, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Gerchik, Paul, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Gershoy, Eugenie, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
    includes photos of Gershoy, 1938, 1940
  - Gikow, Ruth, circa 1938-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Gildersleeve, Jack B., circa 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Gilien, Theodore, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Girolami, George, circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Girouard, Gerard, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Glenn, John S., 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
    includes photos of Glenn, circa 1937
  - Glicenstein, Enrico, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
    includes photos of Glicenstein, 1940
  - Glickman, Maurice, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Glinsky, Vincent, 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
    includes photos of Glinsky
  - Glintenkamp, H., 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Godwin, Earl, 1936-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Goeller, Charles Louis, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Goetz, Esther Becker, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Goldat, Isaac, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Good, Minnetta, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Goodelman, Aaron J., circa 1936-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Goodman, Bertram, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    includes photo of Goodman
  - Goodman, Job, circa 1938-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Goodrich, Gertrude, 1938-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Goolst, Morris, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gordin, Sid, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Gordon, Benjamin, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Gorelick, Boris, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Gorky, Arshile, circa 1935-circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
    includes photos of Gorky
  - Gotcliffe, Sidney, circa 1939-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Gough, W., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Graham, F. Wynn, 1937-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Graham, Mies, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
    photo of Mies
  - Grambs, Blanche, circa 1937-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Grant, Gordon, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Green, Russell, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Green, Wallace, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Greenbaum, James, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Greene, Balcomb, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
    includes photo probably of Greene
  - Greene, G. Peter, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Greene, H., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Greenwood, Marion, 1936-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
    includes photos of Greenwood, 1936, 1940
  - Gregory, John, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Gregory, Peter, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 31)
    includes photo of Gregory
  - Griffith, Herbert, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Grippe, Peter, 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Gropper, William, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Gross, Chaim, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Grossman, Isidore, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Groth, John, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Grunvald, Samuel, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Gubin, Selma, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Guck, Edna, circa 1935-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Guerruiriprbe, Trude, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Guglielmi, O. Louis, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Gunn, Arthur, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Guston, Philip, circa 1939-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 44)
    includes photos of Guston
  - Guteman, Ernest, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Gutieri, Ralph, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Guy, James, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Hague, Raoul, circa 1935-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Halfant, Jules, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hammer, Amelia, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hancke, F., 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hannah, Muriel, circa 1937-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Harari, Hananiah, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hardy, Howard, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Harkavy, Minna R., circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Harlin, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Harmon, Lily, 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Harnly, Perkins, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Harrington, Mabel, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Harris, Louis, 1937-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Harriton, Abraham, circa 1938-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
    includes photos of Harriton, 1938
  - Hart, Agnes, 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hartman, Bertram, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hartman, M., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Hartman, Rosella, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Hartman, Samuel, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Haseltine, Herbert, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Haucke, Frederick, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Haupt, Theodore Gilbert, 1938-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hauser, Alonzo, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hayes, Vertis, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hebald, Milton Elting, circa 1937-circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hecht, Zoltan, circa 1937-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Heckman, Albert William, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Heino, Virka & Otto, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Heinrich, Christian, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Heins, John, circa 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Helfond, Riva, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Heller, Helen West, circa 1936-circa 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
    includes photos of Heller, 1936
  - Henkel, August, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    includes photos of Henkel
  - Henn, Rudolph, 1937-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Henning, Charles, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Henoch, Hanley, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Henricksen, Ralph, circa 1936-circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
    includes photo of Henricksen, 1938
  - Henry, Charles T., 1939-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Hermes, Allen, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Hershman, Edna, circa 1937-circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    includes photos of Hershman, circa 1939
  - Heum, Rudolph, circa 1935-circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)